export const dispenser = {
    dispenses: [
        "2019-10-30T02:17:52.912+00:00",
        "2019-10-30T02:17:53.408+00:00",
        "2019-10-31T02:18:52.000+00:00",
        "2019-10-31T02:16:53.408+00:00",
    ],
    btn1: [
        "2019-10-30T02:16:53.578+00:00",
        "2019-10-30T02:17:57.019+00:00",
    ],
    btn2: [
        "2019-10-30T02:17:52.012+00:00",
    ],
    btn3: [

    ],
}

export const surveys = [
    {
        date: "2019-06-27T19:36:59.095Z",
        responses: [
            {
                question: "family",
                answer: "1"
            },
            {
                question: "recreation",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "social activity",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "occupation",
                answer: "4"
            },
            {
                question: "sexual behavior",
                answer: "5"
            },
            {
                question: "self care",
                answer: "6"
            },
            {
                question: "life support activities",
                answer: "7"
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        date: "2019-06-28T19:36:59.095Z",
        responses: [
            {
                question: "family",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "recreation",
                answer: "1"
            },
            {
                question: "social activity",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "occupation",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "sexual behavior",
                answer: "5"
            },
            {
                question: "self care",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "life support activities",
                answer: "7"
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        date: "2019-06-29T19:36:59.095Z",
        responses: [
            {
                question: "family",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "recreation",
                answer: "1"
            },
            {
                question: "social activity",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "occupation",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "sexual behavior",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "self care",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "life support activities",
                answer: "7"
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        date: "2019-06-30T19:36:59.095Z",
        responses: [
            {
                question: "family",
                answer: "4"
            },
            {
                question: "recreation",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "social activity",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "occupation",
                answer: "1"
            },
            {
                question: "sexual behavior",
                answer: "1"
            },
            {
                question: "self care",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "life support activities",
                answer: "7"
            },
        ]
    },

]